Albert Suñé **Belmonte**

Full-Stack Software Engineer



- □ albert.sune.belmonte@gmail.com
- +34 650 79 39 68
- Carrer Josep de Viure 9, Ripollet, Barcelona, Spain
- https://portfolioalbertsube.netlify.app/
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/albertsube/
- https://github.com/albertsube
- ## 06 Mar 1993



Spanish

Catalan

English FCE

German

AWARDS

Best academic records 2013-14 **UPC**

Sep 2014

Best academic records 2012-13 UPC

Sep 2013



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Automation Team Leader

Dara Pharmaceutical Equipment

Jan 2021 - present | Granollers, Spain

Supervision from the initial phases of the project: mechanical design conceptualization and validation from an automation point of view and software architecture design. Leadership of automation projects for international clients: review of URS, technical overview during design phase, contact with suppliers, integration with customer systems, commissioning of projects "on-site". Organization of the team's activities and planning using Scrum methodology: product backlog, sprint planning and backlog, daily scrum meetings, sprint review. Technical leadership for the team members: smoothing the learning curve of new members, helping develop new skills for the team, unblocking problems to ensure meeting project schedule.

Automation Engineer

Dara Pharmaceutical Equipment

Apr 2017 - Dec 2020 | Granollers, Spain

Programming and commissioning of PLC code for washing, sterilization, filling and closing machinery. Working with different formats of vials, cartridge, syringes and bags of solid, semi-solid and powder product on sterile conditions. Creation of HMI applications with a user-first approach working with different platforms (FactoryTalk ME/SE, Wonderware, zenon). Development of standard and reusable applications following a modular architecture, maintenance of current standard code and continuous improvement of the code to solve scalability and compatibility issues.

EDUCATION

Master in Full-Stack Developement

Nuclio Digital School

Oct 2023 - Mar 2024

Developement of Full-Stack web application using the following technologies: ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, TailwindCSS.

Double Master Degree in Industrial Engineering and Automatics and Robotics

UPC

Sep 2015 - Oct 2018

Average grade: 8.0/10. Honors: Pattern Recognition and Machine Learning.

Bachelor Degree in Industrial Engineering UPC

Sep 2011 - Jun 2015

Average grade: 8.25/10. Honors: Linear Algebra, Calculus I, Chemistry II, Informatics, Economy and Business, Statistics, Statistical techniques for quality, Organization and Management, Optimization and Simulation.

PROFILE

My name is Albert Suñé Belmonte, also known as albertsube. I started programming when I was 14 as an after-school activity. Since then I decided I wanted to focus my career in software developement. Nowadays I'm leading software developement teams in projects for some of the most demanding pharmaceutical compannies.

After finishing my bachellor degree in Industrial Engineering and a double master degree in Automatic and Robotics, I started working as an Automation Engineer in Dara Pharma. I started developing libraries in the R&D department and after 1 and a half years switched to project developement. There, I begun with small and medium projects but quickly transitioned to bigger ones. Thanks to my good performance I became Team Leader.

As a Team Leader I have lead a team of up to 6 programmers in several projects applying SCRUM methodology. I also have been in charged of leading the software development of the two biggest projects of the company with a billing of +\$15M each.

During 2023 I also started my career as a Web Developer with master degree in Full-Stack Development. Since then I have worked in several personal projects, showcasing the skills learned during my studies as well as learning new technologies and applying them to the projects.

inhind

